Five components. What is the
main difference between level 1 and
level 3? At level 3, you are
immersed in the experience, and your body and mind
are in complete bliss. So, the
difference between the second and
third is similar to watching
someone get drunk. I know none of
you have ever been drunk, but
from what you know, if you watch someone get drunk, you first notice that
they become childish, and if they continue drinking,
this phase begins. That's when the heartbeat is just a straight line,
the feeling in your head goes
from happy to unconsciously flat.
That's the difference between two
and three. It's really also true if someone
takes very strong medication, like five
sleeping pills or something, because at first they're
a little happy, and after the
fifth, it's just a
feeling in their mind.
I can't describe what it is. Watching,
the feeling in the body is still like that;
it's very connected,
almost always still good posture and
a good sense of one's body. So, the body
feels very, very strong and
charged, like a ballet.  Dancer,
everything is under tension.
If you have problems in your body,
for example, if you have problems with your knees,
or you've done a really crazy
Ashtanga yoga class,
then you can sit on a chair.
If your knees interrupt your meditation,
then you should sit on a
chair and really try out
different meditation cushions.
Find one that suits you. I
also know a guy, for example, who sits on a
brick; it's right for him.
So physically, you are very firmly grounded.
The mental feeling is that you are beyond the pale, in a state of
mental bliss.
And again, I would like to point out
that it takes about an
hour to
reach this state. So we will only pretend to do it to
cultivate the tameness for it, just like
we did when we
tried to imagine our past lives.
The first few weeks when you try to
imagine your past lives,
then wonderful
stories will come to mind, like from some
movie, like the Fantastic Four,
and suddenly you will have real
memories.
We will try the third stage of the Form
Realm and  If you
imagine yourself doing it, that can really
be the reason you actually
achieve it. So, the body
feels very grounded. The mental
feeling is that
we still have a mind
focused on one point, and
two other things, Kemper and the Czech Republic,
are very strong at this time.
What's nice is that the fire alarm
is the smoke detector. When it
smells the smoke, it goes "bbb bb b p p."
That's another little alarm in your
head. You should
concentrate on the fact that you are your heart, and
it's a straight line.
And when you think of one of his four
coffees,
in this third level, a
fire alarm should
go "phi phi phi phi phi phi phi phi phi phi." And then you try to
use the chamber. He's the one who brings
the mind back to the object. My
father lived by fishing, and in
World War II, he was in the navy,
and that's why he loved the sea so much.
[Music]
When I was 15, I bought a boat.  20
meters long with two torpedoes, and with that
you can really attack big ships.
John F. Kennedy was also a captain on a
PC. It's like it was himself,
and then he went out to sea with it for three or four
days and
played poker and fished. And the
fish is a big one. You're
tied to the fishing boat with a special strap,
and it goes like this: why am
I talking about this? That's the
chamber that goes down, and you
bring it back up. It goes down again,
and you bring it back up.
You don't do it like this; you do
the tail like this again, and then
you pull it back up, and then
relax it like this again, and then you see
how this works. And my father then brought the clay
home so we could gut it.
And you start at the genitals and
cut it open along the belly line,
and then you take out the entrails.
And 15 years later, the doctor
told him, "You have a problem in your heart.
We have to operate on you, but do
n't worry,
we'll take a..."  Blood vessel outside leg and
we'll cut you from the Italians up to your
neck and he calls them in which
I couldn't back then I did
n't know how karma works back then
but thought that's really very
strange
on the third stage the mental
feeling is what a straight line
you're really tired do
you want what is the physical feeling
two mental functions are very very
strong the fire alarm the observer who
watches to see if the mind goes somewhere else instead of
concentrating on the heartbeat
if the mind wanders somewhere else then
probably the strong body back and
that's number two the one ready to
start or did he want to wait until
help has digested everything
is clear to everyone what it is what this
straight line means that means that he has
n't been in the last stage of that was
the sugar
that is rather sluggish the feelings are completely
flat these types someone hits them and
they are just completely neutral not
touched someone cuts them open and they just
look completely neutral
no feelings beyond all feelings